Hey,
are you ready yet?
It's okay.
It won't hurt.
Are you going to
suck my blood?
I won't suck it. Your blood.
Then what will you do?
I'll inject you with poison.
Poison?
That's right. Poison.
I'll inject you with my poison.
It will make you unable to ever leave me.
It's okay.
It won't hurt.
Get ready.
There, all done.
Now you can't leave me.
We'll always be together, in life and death.
Are you prepared?
I'm not prepared.
But the curse has already been laid.
So you're my servant now.
My escort.
My beloved.
I love you, Taito.
But even if you say that, all of a sudden...
It's fine.
Just say that you love me, Taito.
With that, the black magic will be complete.
Or do you dislike me?
I don't dislike you.
Do you like me then?
Yeah.
Then say it.
Okay. I...
I love you too.
Himea.
That very moment,
the world and my own body completely changed.
A curse has been laid upon me.
Black magic has affected me.
And then...
I love you, Taito.
And so my story began.
Or it was supposed to.
Taito.
Taito!
I...
I love...
Taito! Come on, Taito!
Hey!
Come on now, it's time to wake up!
Homeroom ended long ago.
「900 seconds of afterschool 」
Huh, Haruka? What's wrong?
That isn't what you should be saying, you know.
You've been sleeping since the fifth period.
Not even the teacher could wake you up.
Huh?! Homeroom ended?!
That's what I said. Are you all right?
Damn, I sure overslept.
Ha-Haruka, wh-what are you doing?!
Eh? Oh, you were drooling.
I was drooling?
No, this is...
Um...
I knew it.
And Haruka was supposed to be my wife.
Haruka, you know, we're not like that, right?
So don't do that again, okay?
Hmm? We're not what?
You know, right?
Hmm?
Well, whatever.
Wow, you're still tired?
What?
Are you feeling sick or something, Taito?
Not really. I'm fine.
Does your leg still hurt?
Nope.
But...
Oh, right, Haruka.
Yes?
Lately I've been having this same dream.
Huh? Dream?
Yeah.
What kind of dream?
I'm not telling. You'll just laugh.
Aww, no way! Now I'm curious!
You won't laugh?
I won't laugh.
Oh, okay. Then I guess I can tell you.
I'm a kid, and some girl confesses to me.
"I love you, Taito," she says.
Huh, what's that all about?
That's the dream you keep having?
You said you wouldn't laugh!
Sorry, I just had to.
I'm sorry.
I wonder how old I was...
Actually, could the girl in my dream be you,
Haruka?
Th-That can't be!
I haven't confessed to you or anything yet.
You're right! She was like, so cute!
Wha- That's so mean!
Sorry 'bout that.
It's Gekkou-sama!
Gekkou-sama, Gekkou-sama! Look at me!
Gekkou-sama, are you here on official student council work?
You're in the way, small fry.
Stay out of my sight.
How unfair! Please raise your voice to me too!
Move, move!
Hey, Gekkou! Can't I just beat 'em up?
Don't do anything unnecessary, trash.
I'm not trash!
Gekkou-sama! Work hard!
An excellent student and a splendid sportsman,
who's also popular with the girls.
The superstar who joined the student council right after he entered high school.
The graceful passing of Kurenai Gekkou-sama, huh?
Ah, Taito, you're jealous of Kurenai-kun's popularity, aren't you?
I guess so.
Oh, my. So you want to be popular?
If I said I didn't, I'd be lying.
But I'm not some superman,
so I'll never be as popular as him.
You'd rather date someone like him, wouldn't you, Haruka?
Now, now. I wonder about that.
What's that mean?
Haruka's actually quite cute.
But... what's this?
Taito!
You're my servant.
My escort.
My beloved.
I love you, Taito.
Taito?
I'm fine! I'm just a bit wobbly because I slept too much.
Say, Haruka?
Did he just look at me?
Kurenai-kun? Weren't you just imagining that, Taito?
Really? It felt like he was glaring at me, though.
Oh, well.
I wonder what people like him think about all day.
Yeah, he's quite awesome and all.
Yeah, my very ordinary life is completely different to his.
You're not ordinary, Taito.
I sure am.
No, you're not.
But I am.
Say, what if I say there's nothing wrong with being ordinary?
Huh?
If you can just live in peace and smile every day, that's the best you could hope for.
Right?
I guess so.
I forgot! The tennis club has a meeting today!
Sorry, Taito! Can you wait until it's over?
No way.
Eh? You meanie! Let's go home together!
Just get going already.
Ah, right.
See you!
Ah, Haruka!
What?
Well, maybe it's fine being ordinary.
I know, right?
Though saying that makes me sound more like an old geezer than a high school student.
Taito-jiichan, watch out for cars on your way home.
Ordinary, huh?
All right!
Walking won't be a problem.
But any intense activity is...
After that injury caused me to lose all that I'd worked so hard for,
Haruka...
It's okay, Taito.
Taito!
...was always there by my side, smiling,
saying everything would be just fine.
Taito.
She entered the same high school,
where she would be by my side saying
If you can just live in peace and smile every day, that's the best you could hope for.
Well, maybe I should find something to do already.
Student Council
Kiss me!
Kiss me, Gekkou!
Shut up.
What? Shut up?! What's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, are you even listening to me?! Hurry up and kiss me already!
Hurry, hurry! I'll die if you don't!
Come on, Gekkou!
It came through!
Just hurry up and kiss me already!
I'll die!
I really will die!
I'll die! I'll die!
Gekkou!
Shut up, small fry.
Exorcise, Spell Error.
Small fry.
What are you doing, Gekkou?! That was dangerous!
You can't handle a weak foe like this if I don't kiss you, small fry?
I'm not small fry!
Fine. Annoying small fry.
I'm thirsty! Some Dr Cinnamon would do well!
Can I go buy some?
Simpleton. Do as you wish.
Yay! I'll buy some for you too!
I'm off!
Say, what do you want, Gekkou?
Cola.
Okay!
It's crap.
Utter crap.
This plot.
Most Ancient Sorcerer Saitohimea
Sacrifice Kurogane Taito
Also regarding Kurenai Gekkou
It's a crappy plot.
Most Ancient Sorcerer Saitohimea
Sacrifice Kurogane Taito
Also regarding Kurenai Gekkou
Dr Cinnamon! Dr Cinnamon! It's tasty but unpopular.
Wasn't she with Kurenai Gekkou earlier?
Oh shi-
Run!
Am I dying?
Sorry, Haruka.
Taito...
You haven't come...
Aren't you coming soon?
I've...
...been alone in here all this time.
Taito, I'm lonely.
Come here, quick.
Just one more time...
I'll wait another five minutes.
I wonder if you'll come.
Taito...
Taito!
Himea! Himea!
Taito said he had fun being with me.
When I was with Taito,
I was so happy.
Taito, you were the only one who didn't try to use me and my power.
You said it was fun being with me.
Taito...
Taito, I want to see you.
If Taito has forgotten about me...
If Taito has found happiness...
I don't mind being forgotten.
No.
No!
That was a lie! Please don't forget!
Don't forget me, Taito!
Hey!
Hey! Are you alive?
Great, you're safe.
Hey! I can see your panties!
Huh?
No way. Isn't that actually... me?!
Wow, awesome! How come you're still alive?
You some headless human?
No, more importantly, isn't that body over there me?
Yeah.
I-I knew it...
Wow, you still feel pain, even if your head isn't attached?
No way...
I can move?
What's this? How come it moves?
That doesn't really matter now!
Are you a transformable robot?!
Your reaction is totally off!
M-M-Monster!
Ah! It's a hit and run! Take a picture!
What?
Oh shi-
Here! Come here! All right!
Wow! Bye bye, Immortal-kun!
A-Anyway, I gotta do something about my head.
I-It reattached. Everything is okay now!
Like hell I am!
Not a scratch...
A-And my leg... I could run at full strength...
The hell?
Didn't I just die?
Just what the hell is going on?!
My power...
My power is coming back!
I see. Taito...
He died once for me.
Vanish!
Now...
Now I can finally finish it.
The 900-second black magic.
Now, remember.
Call my name.
When you do, all of my power will return.
I love you, Taito!
That... That voice from my dream...
No,
I know it.
I met her a long time ago.
We'll always be together, in life and death.
Her... name...
I love you, Taito.
Hi...me...a...
That's right.
Saitohimea.
Taito...
You remembered.
He'll come to get me any time now.
Wait, my appearance...
I have to do something about this.
Let's see... Right now my body is that of a six year old, and nine years have passed...
So, 15 should be right, huh?
I wonder if Taito will tell me I'm cute.
Well, if he doesn't...
I'll kill him.
Military
It's me.
What?
Damn!
Shit!
Damn it! I'm the worst!
How many years have I kept Himea waiting?
Himea!
I... I definitely won't forget you!
Quietly quivering to the end of our memories
tsuioku no hate ni shizuka ni yurameku
追憶の果てに静かに揺らめく
I'll come and save you, Himea.
So just...
Why? Why did I forget?
An everlasting, distant promise
eien ni tsuzuku haruka no yakusoku
永遠に続く遥かの約束
Idiot!
Drowned in sorrow, a breaking cicada
kanashimi ni noreta utsusemi kowashite
悲しみに濡れた空蝉壊して
Huh? It healed?
I see! This is the power Himea granted me!
Replacing the despair, the loneliness was standing out
zetsubou wo surikaete kodoku wa medatteta
絶望をすり替えて孤独は目立ってた
Himea. I promised...
Until the day I meet with you alone
tada hitori kimi ni deau hi made
ただひとり君に出会う日まで
to never let you go. To always protect you.
In that park... In that park were we used to play together...
Come here, let's put our hearts together
koko e oide kokoro kasaneyou
ここへおいで　心重ねよう
Himea.
I'll remove your thorns for you
Himea!
kimi no toge o torisatte ageru
君の棘を取り去ってあげる
Play to our crumbled future
kuzure ochita mirai e kanaderu
崩れ落ちた未来へ奏でる
Scream out louder and then let us kiss
sakebigoe wo hiroi agete kuchizuke kawasou
叫び声を拾い上げて口付け交わそう
Wait for me, Himea!
Come here, let's put our hearts together
koko e oide kokoro kasaneyou
ここへおいで　心重ねよう
Play to our crumbled future
kuzure ochita mirai e kanaderu
崩れ落ちた未来へ奏でる
It hasn't changed at all, huh?
This place was always empty, for some reason or another.
Himea...
Wait.
Why did I expect Himea to be waiting for me here?
Himea!
You're late! You took too long!
Himea...
Another five minutes...
For nine years...
I kept telling myself, just another five minutes...
If you didn't show up, I would kill you.
I've been waiting all this time...
All this time?
You waited for nine years?
And you said just another five minutes?
Himea...
I'm sorry. I know I promised, but...
I missed you, Taito.
Himea...
I'm sorry I've have kept you waiting.
No.
You're here now, so I'll forgive you.
Our deeply entangled fates and stories
began moving towards their goal.
Listen up, trash. I am Kurenai Gekkou, president of the student council.
From today on and forever, you'll be my slaves.
Kneel down before me and worship me.
Be grateful that you have the chance to serve me.
Because standing before you now is a real genius.
What? Got a problem with that?
If you got a problem, step forth. I'll kill you.
Next time   「900 seconds of afterschool 」
The rest of you are all my slaves